var title = 'Traduza para grego.<br>Para substantivos, inclua o artigo definido (ο, η, το...).';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "a música",
   answer: ["η μουσική", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "as espécies",
   answer: ["τα είδη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a garagem",
   answer: ["το γκαράζ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "os átomos, os indivíduos",
   answer: ["τα άτομα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "as importações",
   answer: ["οι εισαγωγές", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "monótono",
   answer: ["μονότονος", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a vergonha",
   answer: ["η ντροπή", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o desastre",
   answer: ["η συμφορά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o comércio",
   answer: ["το εμπόριο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a benção",
   answer: ["η ευλογία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o carro, automóvel",
   answer: ["το αυτοκίνητο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o amanhã",
   answer: ["το αύριο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a quinta-feira",
   answer: ["η Πέμπτη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];